sendspace.com 2019-12-28

# sendspace | Privacy Policy

Please read this entire notice. **_send_ space** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the **_send_ space** Web site, **Wizard Desktop** app, and **SendSpace for Android** app.

By using **_send_ space**, future products, services or features we develop and introduce, or our website (together the "Services"), you consent to the collection, processing and disclosure of data concerning you in accordance with this privacy policy.If you do not agree with any of the terms of this policy, please do not use our Site, **Wizard Desktop** app or **SendSpace for Android** app. We reserve the right to alter our privacy policy at any time. We will notify you of any alterations with reasonable notice through the service, such as by posting it on our website, by email, or otherwise. If you do not agree to the altered privacy policy, you may stop using our Services. 

* There are situations when using **_send_ space** when we may need personal information from you. By "personal information" we mean information that is uniquely identified to you, such as your name, email address, IP address, password and user name. **_send_ space** does not collect and transmit personal or sensitive user data unrelated to functionality.

This may include information about your operating system, device identifier, carrier, language, battery performance, wi-fi or other network connections, or other data that you permit the App to access on your device including through permissions on your device (e.g. Google Play on Android).

We may disclose in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties, such as advertisers or potential advertisers. Those disclosures do not include personal information.

**_send_ space** might use information collected in connection with your participation in interactive activities, including account registration, for its own internal purposes, such as (by way of illustration) to respond to inquiries, to enforce the Terms of Use, or to defend itself in the event of litigation.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer _send_ space. We also can use the IP address to verify the identity of perpetrators of illegal activity.

We may retain information regarding you and your use of the Services, including personally identifying information, for as long as needed to provide you with the Services and the uses described in this Privacy Policy.

* **_send_ space** will not sell any of your personal information to third parties. We may access, use, preserve, and share your information, including your personally identifying information, with third parties when we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to: detect, prevent and address fraud and other illegal activity; protect ourselves, you and others, including as part of investigations; or prevent death or imminent bodily harm.We may also share such information if we believe that you have abused your rights to use the Services or violated an applicable law, or in connection with any dispute between you and us with respect to the Services.

You assume the risk that a court or government agency may order **_send_ space** to disclose your submission and/or personally identifying information about you, or that a litigant, a court, a grand jury, or government agency may subpoena that information. If a governmental agency (for example, law enforcement agencies, US Attorneys' offices or similar governmental agencies) sends us a subpoena, we will comply with it.

We will usually attempt to notify you of such a subpoena or other legal process by sending a notice by electronic mail to the most recent e-mail address you have provided to us, if you have registered. The notice will include basic information concerning the subpoena, court order, or legal process (i.e., name of lawsuit, case number, place of filing, party issuing subpoena, the court where the subpoena was issued, contact information, deadline by which we plan to comply with the process, etc.).

**_send_ space** may need to consult its own attorneys. In doing so, **_send_ space** may disclose personal information to its attorneys.

We cannot advise you regarding the law or an appropriate response to a subpoena. Should you wish to oppose a subpoena or other legal process, you should seek legal advice concerning applicable rights and procedures that might be available.

* We may collect information about your use of our Services through the use of cookies, pixels or similar technologies. For example, we may use this information to provide or improve our Services, for measurement and analytics to better understand how our services function and are used, or for internal operations. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on your mobile phone, computer, or other device. Pixels, often used in connection with cookies, are small instances of code placed in webpages that do things like allow another server to measure how frequently webpages are viewed and used. **_send_ space** will not distribute or sell any of your personal information to third parties.

By using _send_ space, you are consenting to our use of cookies and other tracking technology in accordance with this notice. If you do not agree to our use of cookies and other tracking technology in this way, you should set your browser settings accordingly or not use the _send_ space Site. If you disable cookies that we use, this may impact your user experience.

* **_send_ space** has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We upload your information from your device over a secured connection to our servers. We back up the data on a daily basis, and have password protected access levels which insure legitimate use.

The **_send_ space** website and our SendSpace for Android app may include links to other Web sites, usually via advertising. **_send_ space** is not responsible for the security practices of the Web sites that are linked from our site. We highly recommend that visitors check the privacy statements at these linked sites.

* **_send_ space** does not require users to register. Any personal data you do provide will be kept no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data is processed. GDPR defines personal data as "any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person"

**_send_ space** uses a third-party payment processing company. We are not provided with a copy of your financial information such as card number, personal address etc. and it is not stored on our servers.

We will erase your personal data upon request, if there is no other legal requirement to maintain certain data for a reasonable period of time.

**_send_ space** has taken steps to ensure your personal data receives a "reasonable" level of data protection and privacy. We use secure HTTPS for all communications and important data such as your password is stored in encoded form.

**_send_ space** will report data breaches to supervisory authorities and registered individuals affected by any breach within 72 hours of when the breach was detected.

* **_send_ space** provides users with the opportunity to change or modify or delete information previously provided. If you would like to change or modify your information, please visit your 'My Account' page at our site or check the various app settings.

* Any questions relating to our Privacy Policies may be directed to **_send_ space** using the website contact form.
